<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basketball on Jared DeHaan&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>/categories/basketball/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basketball on Jared DeHaan&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/basketball/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is Kofi Cockburn ready for the NBA or should he go back to Illinois for one more season?</title>
      <link>/2021/04/21/is-kofi-cockburn-ready-for-the-nba-or-should-he-go-back-to-illinois-for-one-more-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/21/is-kofi-cockburn-ready-for-the-nba-or-should-he-go-back-to-illinois-for-one-more-season/</guid>
      <description>Illinois had a terrific season thanks to future first round pick Ayo Dosunmu and Kofi Cockburn. Yes, I know this name sounds very funny but it’s pronounced like Coburn with no c and k.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who was the worst offensive college basketball team this season?</title>
      <link>/2021/04/21/who-was-the-worst-offensive-college-basketball-team-this-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/21/who-was-the-worst-offensive-college-basketball-team-this-season/</guid>
      <description>The constant questions you see are who is the best team in a particular season or who is the best player or players. I want to do a different spin and see who was the worst team(s) during the 2020-2021 NCAA basketball season on the offensive side of the ball. This Covid stricken season has been very odd and many teams had difficulty playing all their games due to cancellations and postponements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois missed their chance</title>
      <link>/2021/03/27/illinois-missed-their-chance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/03/27/illinois-missed-their-chance/</guid>
      <description>Illinois was a heavy favorite to win the 2021 NCAA Basketball National Championship but instead got ousted by the NCAA powerhouse Loyola Chicago in the Round of 32. I will be digging deep into stats to discover exactly why Illinois exited the tournament earlier than expected.
I first loaded four libraries that I might need for my data into my project.
library(tidyverse) ## ── Attaching packages ─────────────────────────────────────── tidyverse 1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
